{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.8.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":2007,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":16,"width":970,"height":535,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"SmartShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":"If the abandon code is “Part Taken to QAR (Q)”, go to the RMVUC screen. Enter the license plate information (701551095), in the “License Plate” field. Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_1","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["701551095"]},"constraints":{"length":9}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_1","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_1","title":"Click the white box and type 701551095 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_1","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12114","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_1","Text_Entry_Box_1","Success_Shape_1","Hint_Shape_1","Failure_Shape_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12114"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"If the license plate has an “Available” status, move the license plate (701551095) to QAR, by pressing F3. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_2","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_2","title":"Press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12216","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_2","Text_Entry_Box_2","Hint_Shape_2"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12216"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":"To move the license plate (701551095) to QAR, type ISPMH in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_3","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["ISPMH"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_2","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_3","title":"Click the white box and type ISPMH. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_2","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12344","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_3","Text_Entry_Box_3","Success_Shape_2","Hint_Shape_3","Failure_Shape_2"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12344"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":"Enter the License Plate number (701551095) in the “LP” field, then press the Tab key to the “From Loc” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_4","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["701551095"]},"constraints":{"length":9}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_3","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_4","title":"Click the white box and type 701551095 then press the Tab key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_3","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12472","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_4","Text_Entry_Box_4","Success_Shape_3","Hint_Shape_4","Failure_Shape_3"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12472"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":"Press the Tab key to the “To Loc” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_6","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_7","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_5","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_5","title":"Press the Tab key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12596","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_5","SmartShape_6","SmartShape_7","Text_Entry_Box_5","Hint_Shape_5"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12596"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_6","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["QAR001A1Y"]},"constraints":{"length":9}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_8","title":"Enter the QAR location (QAR001A1Y) and press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_4","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_6","title":"Click the white box and type QAR001A1Y then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_4","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12724","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_6","SmartShape_8","Success_Shape_4","Hint_Shape_6","Failure_Shape_4"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12724"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"To choose the highlighted license plate and its quantity, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_7","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_7","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12826","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_9","Text_Entry_Box_7","Hint_Shape_7"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12826"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_10","title":"Enter the quantity to move (1), then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_8","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["1"]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_5","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_8","title":"Click the white box and type 1 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_5","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12954","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_10","Text_Entry_Box_8","Success_Shape_5","Hint_Shape_8","Failure_Shape_5"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12954"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_11","title":"Press Enter to assign the inventory to the new location. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_9","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_9","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13056","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_11","Text_Entry_Box_9","Hint_Shape_9"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13056"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_12","title":"Press N for “No” in response to the “Create RF work?” message. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_10","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["N"]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_6","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_10","title":"Click the white box and type N. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_6","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13184","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_12","Text_Entry_Box_10","Success_Shape_6","Hint_Shape_10","Failure_Shape_6"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13184"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_13","title":"The system will automatically generate the next license plate that can be moved. To exit the “Pallet Moving” screen, press and hold the Ctrl and C keys. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_11","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_11","title":"Press and hold the Ctrl and C keys. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13286","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_13","Text_Entry_Box_11","Hint_Shape_11"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13286"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_14","title":"Press the Esc key to exit the screen and return to the “DALLAS SYSTEM MENUS” screen. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_12","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_12","title":"Press  the Esc key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13388","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_14","Text_Entry_Box_12","Hint_Shape_12"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13388"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_15","title":"To verify the status of a part, press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_13","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["P"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_13","title":"Press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13490","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_15","Text_Entry_Box_13","Hint_Shape_13"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13490"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_16","title":"To verify the status of a part, type IPLMA in the “Trans ID” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_14","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IPLMA"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_7","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_14","title":"Click the white box and type IPLMA. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_7","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13618","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_16","Text_Entry_Box_14","Success_Shape_7","Hint_Shape_14","Failure_Shape_7"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13618"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_17","title":"Enter the Product number (84311584). Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_15","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["84311584"]},"constraints":{"length":8}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_8","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_15","title":"Click the white box and type 84311584 then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_8","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13746","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_17","Text_Entry_Box_15","Success_Shape_8","Hint_Shape_15","Failure_Shape_8"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13746"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_18","title":"View the product information. You have completed this process. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_19","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13809","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_18","SmartShape_19"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":207},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13809"}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"PartTakentoQARStep4TrainingTWO","class":"project","title":"PartTakentoQARStep4TrainingTWO","children":["Slide12114","Slide12216","Slide12344","Slide12472","Slide12596","Slide12724","Slide12826","Slide12954","Slide13056","Slide13184","Slide13286","Slide13388","Slide13490","Slide13618","Slide13746","Slide13809"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":[],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"launch_content","SCCriteria":"launch_content","exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide12114","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12216","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide12344","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide12472","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide12596","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide12724","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide12826","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide12954","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide13056","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide13184","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide13286","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide13388","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide13490","title":"Slide 13"},{"id":"Slide13618","title":"Slide 14"},{"id":"Slide13746","title":"Slide 15"},{"id":"Slide13809","title":"Slide 16"}]}